I'm impressed she managed to catch up to us.
Not that it matters, though.
Now, come on.
We mustn't leave our boat waiting.
Chosha-sumu!
Hey!
Oh, God.
Right on time.
Liu Guang?
What the hell?
The riverside?
How did I get here?
You hurt?
She's getting away!
Get her!
Liu Guang!
Go, go on!
Why did he get on the boat?
Captain Xiao! Wang Zhan!
Hurry! Take her for rescue!
Captain Xiao! Are you okay?
What happened to you, sir?
Go get the rest of the guys!
Tell every damn cop in this city!
Daddy, don't stop busting down doors until we find Li Tien Xie!
Well, should I play host?
There's no such thing as flawless.
But it's nice when plans go smoothly.
What's he doing here?
Well, he crashed my exit.
I was just going to leave with nothing, but then he grabbed me.
They couldn't have known about the rendezvous.
And yet, here we are!
What the hell was he thinking?
None of this makes any sense.
It was just you?
Yes, us three.
And then he'd lock the door when we heard the crash.
The surveillance?
We checked.
The camera spotted Mr. Liu exiting his room after we had rushed in to help.
With all the commotion of the broken window and trying to get into the room, we didn't notice him.
Captain Xiao!
Any news on Liu Guang?
Easy. Catch your breath.
We don't know much.
Just that he snuck out on his own.
That said, the bigger question is why.
Damn it.
This shouldn't have happened.
But I let her possess me.
That's not your fault, okay?
No one knew what would happen.
I've got men scouring the city.
Just wait.
All right?
We'll find Liu Guang and Li Tianxie.
This case is top priority.
And I've found something big.
Chen Xin.
Chen Xin was lead on the case?
And it gets worse.
The murder of Liu Lan and her husband?
That was his last case before he quit.
It wasn't long after his resignation that the files for Li Tianxie and Li Tianxien mysteriously vanished.
But they never existed.
My guess, Chen Xin is still tied up in all of this.
That could be why he sent men after you.
And why he'd be working with Liu Jing.
I have some eyes on him.
But we can't do anything yet.
We need more.
Be careful.
All you've done is secure the scene, correct?
And nothing more?
Right.
We did a rough search when we swept the room.
Didn't touch anything.
And there?
We didn't get to it, sir.
They probably hid in here after breaking the window.
Waited.
And snuck out.
About 20 minutes later,
he catches up to you at the river.
Not a single second wasted.
Suggests a plan.
Oh.
Liu Guang also sent me an address,
which is why I went to the river in the first place.
Hey, this his phone?
Yeah, that's his.
Well then,
seems like he's leaving us breadcrumbs.
Do either of you know his password?
Yeah, I do.
091305.
All right, we're in.
Can't believe he trusted you with his password.
Is that number significant to him somehow?
Maybe?
Maybe.
He doesn't know I know it.
Say what?
There's just a missed call from you.
What about his photos?
Huh?
That's the view from here.
But why would he take this?
Hang on.
Could he…
I think I know why.
It's for you to go back to that moment.
When was it taken?
That's the exact time I got the address he sent me.
Just before we left,
I noticed Luke Wong seemed worried.
Let's go.
I'll give you a rundown on how to talk to the witness
on the ride over to the station.
Right.
We all were then.
Which is why I find it hard to believe
that he just wanted to capture the view.
He wanted a backup plan.
So he took the photo as a marker,
hoping we'd find it.
He wanted to make sure we still had options.
If things got really bad.
That explains how he was acting at the river.
Even with Master Suen's lessons,
Luke Wong's not a strong fighter.
But when he fought Li Tianxi,
he was holding his own.
With how impulsive he was,
it would make more sense if you were possessing him.
So I've already used the photo?
Or I will.
But what happens if I don't?
Would I have gotten on the boat at Li Tianxi?
Uh, Captain?
What is he talking about?
Look,
they're going through something right now.
Do you mind giving us the room?
Yeah, sure.
Lu Guang,
did you see this coming?
Is that why you couldn't let them take me?
The half-dead idiot is bleeding out all over the floor.
And I don't want to deal with the corpse.
We need a way to bring Cheng Xiaoxie here.
He's the only thing that matters.
Once we have him,
we can rewrite all of it.
You got something?
And you're absolutely sure that it's her?
That it's Li Tianxi?
Yes, sir.
Police in the Nanda district got a report two days ago.
Oh, man.
This place used to be packed.
Now it's just abandoned.
Yeah, that's what happens.
People move out and don't come back.
Huh?
Hang on.
I think I just heard something.
Yeah, so what?
Come on, let's go.
No, listen.
Sounds like someone's in there.
Or it's a ghost and we should leave.
What?
Dude, come on.
Let's look.
Fine, but you're dying first.
You're too kind.
Now lift.
Huh?
Still got power.
Awesome.
He's the only thing that matters.
Once we have him,
we can rewrite all of it.
Anyone here?
Even finding that sister of yours.
Two kids found her
when they broke into an abandoned grocery store.
She's not in the system,
but her physical description
matches with Li Tianxi perfectly.
All right.
There's no more room for mistakes.
The police would have found your sister by now.
It's a pity.
I can't abide betrayal.
Even from her.
She's beyond mercy now.
That can't be our only option.
That depends.
What would you suggest?
What's our new endgame?
Captain Shao, please calm down.
She's only just arrived at the station.
We haven't confirmed it's her.
What happened on the boat after you left?
Tell me!
Is he safe?
Where is he?
Wait, where are you?
All right.
Everyone take a breath.
She might not be the Li Tianxi
we've been dealing with.
Why does everyone keep saying that like it's true?
How is she any different?
Sir,
she hasn't said a word since she got here.
And it's possible she can't.
Developmentally,
she still seems like a child.
So that's actually her,
and we've been dealing with her brother.
But then why would he go through all that trouble?
Was it all just to kidnap you?
I guess so.
He's likely the one who's been controlling people too.
Not just one at a time either, apparently.
But I never saw him activate his powers.
Then use the photo from Lu Guang to find out.
Avoiding history doesn't mean you've changed it.
So don't.
The past will be just as it was.
A lot could have happened.
But Lu Guang made a choice.
And now that choice is fate.
Past or future.
Remain untouched.
You're right.
Thanks.
We've been trying to get through to her,
but nothing seems to work.
Won't even eat.
If we push her,
she'll probably shut down and give us nothing.
Let's leave her alone.
We can find a psychologist to talk with her in the morning.
We don't have that kind of time.
Her brother's holding someone hostage.
Get help.
And do it fast.
Captain,
I have an idea.
Keep making calls in the meantime.
Okay.
I'm gonna need some things.
Hello.
That's fine. You can drink it when you want to.
It's funny, I knew a kid. He used to hate drinking his milk.
There! Drink it!
No! Gross!
You don't know that! You haven't even tried it yet!
Don't be a butt and drink it!
No way!
You're not gonna get tall if you don't drink it!
No! That's a lie! You're stupid!
You're the one who's being stupid!
Hey, you're such a jerk, Chow Ling!
You're not my boss!
You're just a…
A big, mean, stinky girl tiger!
I'm Cheng Shao Shi!
I'm a big dummy with a straw piss nose!
No, I'm not!
I'm gonna make you look so much uglier!
Just watch me!
He was so mad he started chugging his milk as fast as he could, which made me laugh more.
The more I laughed, the faster he drank till it was gone.
Then he drew me on his milk carton and it was so funny.
I always thought of myself as his big sister.
And yet, he's older than me.
Now he's grown up and he ended up getting tall.
He's so tough and strong but still kinda careless.
Like a kid.
But now when he has to do things he doesn't like, he faces them head on.
And it's all thanks to me getting him to drink his milk.
Hey, don't you have a brother?
Do you have any stories about him?
What a clever little brain you have.
It's why you're a good partner.
So why don't you be a good partner to me and tell me how you knew the when and where of our plan.
Why would I do that?
You'll just kill me once I do.
Well now you've gone and made me angry.
And I don't wanna be nice anymore.
Now, let's see.
How close do I wanna bring you to death?
Well now you're just a lie.
Let's see.
How close do I want noone in the game?
How close do I want noone in the game, I don't wanna bring you to death like Krishi!
I don't wanna connect that to a증 is my life.
Come keep it.
You're the THAT responsible method of taking care of all the hell with advice.
And I'm sure you could be completelyсти to a reality.
What are you doing with the events like Krishi?
Let's go.
What do I do now?